{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_6_SW8LH5",
                "player_3_SW8LH5",
                "player_9_SW8LH5",
                "player_11_SW8LH5"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                6,
                3,
                9,
                11
            ],
            "animation": [
                "pick_up",
                "liedown",
                "crouch",
                "stand"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots",
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A man with short black hair, wearing a white button-up shirt, dark pants, and black shoes. Light skin tone."
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    16472.434,
                    -80725.415,
                    5793.474,
                    0.0,
                    -90.001,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    16680.849,
                    -81265.999,
                    5656.993,
                    0,
                    56.64769561800071,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    16746.471,
                    -81653.756,
                    5604.322,
                    0,
                    -63.405373098192285,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    16826.044,
                    -81579.186,
                    5607.509,
                    0,
                    -60.88342569362456,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            16074.472,
            -81380.192,
            5768.077
        ],
        "sample_radius": 993.8772989851803
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            17451.468,
            -81753.152,
            5420.3,
            0,
            149.84677406394272,
            0
        ],
        [
            16533.718,
            -82367.362,
            5642.03,
            0,
            82.08467883840484,
            0
        ],
        [
            16036.294,
            -80773.7,
            5809.578,
            0,
            -39.51790648008346,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_woman_in_deep_V_top or the_man_in_blue_polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_deep_V_top",
                    "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many people are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many individuals are in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many women are in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many men are observed in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many people with light skin color are present?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many individuals with black skin color are in the scene?",
                "answer": "one"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. holding an object",
                    "B. crouching",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "A. holding an object"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman in the deep V-neck top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. lying down",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. jumping"
                ],
                "answer": "A. lying down"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. sit",
                    "D. run"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. sit",
                    "C. lie down",
                    "D. walk"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. In front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. In front of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. Slightly below and to the back-left of",
                    "C. Directly above",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Slightly below and to the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in white shirt relative to the woman in black vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. In front of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the man in white shirt relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Directly behind",
                    "B. Slightly above and to the front-right of",
                    "C. To the front-left of",
                    "D. Below"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Slightly above and to the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "D. To the right of"
            }
        }
    }
}